<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<dublin_core schema="dc">
  <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="none" language="en">9781905586592</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="none" language="en">015e5a16-6cbb-4231-93b3-f1b700678949</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="identifier" qualifier="none" language="en">27d43364-76e7-4622-b3c3-4858ae996f96</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="language" qualifier="none" language="en">en</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="date" qualifier="none" language="en">2012-08-13T22:00:00+00:00</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="publisher" qualifier="none" language="en">Fandemonium Books</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="toc" language="en">Chapter 1: Lifepod -- Chapter 2: Down -- Chapter 3: Queen’s Return -- Chapter 4: Traveling -- Chapter 5: Proving Ground -- Chapter 6: Hunger -- Chapter 7: Home -- Chapter 8: Suspicion -- Chapter 9: Isolation -- Chapter 10: Acceptable Risks -- Chapter 11: Prisons -- Chapter 12: Christmas in October -- Chapter 13: Passages and Pomegranate Seeds -- Chapter 14: Osprey -- Chapter 15: Hidden Things -- Chapter 16: The Skies of Sateda -- Chapter 17: The Old One’s Tale -- Chapter 18: Bloodtainted -- Chapter 19: First Mothers -- Chapter 20: Pilgrims -- Chapter 21: A Door Into Summer -- Chapter 22: Underground -- Chapter 23: Osprey’s Daughters -- Chapter 24: Fair One -- Chapter 25: A Winter’s Night -- Chapter 26: The Brotherhood -- Chapter 27: Reunion -- Chapter 28: Children of the Ancients -- Chapter 29: In From the Cold</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="description" qualifier="none" language="en">&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Old secrets, new truths…&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is the aftermath of battle. Scattered and struggling to regroup, Colonel Sheppard’s team face their darkest days yet in the war against the Wraith Queen, Death.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Continuing her perilous masquerade as Queen Steelflower, Teyla Emmagan’s friendship with Guide grows stronger.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With his help she must journey into the Wraith’s distant past to uncover the shocking truth about their origin – and the key to Queen Death’s defeat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Rodney McKay has a different battle to fight as he struggles to regain his humanity in the face of the atrocity the Wraith have committed against him.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With his life hanging in the balance, will Rodney be forced to do the unthinkable in order to survive…?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SECRETS&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“IS COLONEL Sheppard with you?”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No.” Sam wondered if she looked as perplexed as she sounded.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“He’s not back?”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No.” Woolsey’s face was drawn. “We haven’t heard a word from any of the team. Nothing.” His voice sharpened. “I thought they were to return with you.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam shook her head. “That was the original plan, but we had trouble getting in close enough to beam them out. I had a radio message from Sheppard that indicated they had been beamed aboard Todd’s hive ship. I thought they’d be back by now.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No,” Woolsey said. “We don’t know anything.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam blew out a breath. If Todd were holding them prisoner they’d be getting demands any time now. But that was less likely, given that Teyla was still masquerading as his queen. “It’s possible that the hive ship also took some battle damage,” she said. “That may be more of a priority than getting to a gate and reporting in.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A twitch of Woolsey’s eyebrows showed what he thought of Sheppard’s enthusiasm for immediately reaching a gate and reporting in. “Did they recover Dr. McKay?”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know,” Sam said. “There was a lot of interference on the radio. Sheppard said they were aboard Todd’s ship, but I don’t know if they had McKay with them or not.” She shook her head. “If not, he’s dead. Queen Death’s hive ship exploded. There would have been no survivors…”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="title" qualifier="none" language="en">SGA [20] - Legacy [05] - Secrets</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author" language="en">Melissa Scott</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="author" language="en">Jo Graham</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="contributor" qualifier="none" language="en">calibre (0.9.9) [http://calibre-ebook.com]</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="subject" qualifier="none" language="en">Media Tie-In</dcvalue>
  <dcvalue element="subject" qualifier="none" language="en">Science Fiction</dcvalue>
</dublin_core>
